zeno.fm 2019-11-14

# Zeno Media Privacy Policy

Privacy
Zeno Media Privacy Policy
Zeno Media, LLC
Version Date: March 6 2018
GENERAL
Zeno Media LLC (“Company” or “we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of
its users (“user” or “you”) whether you access our services via a telephone,
wireless or wired device, a partner’s website, through a browser, website
widget, player, a mobile application, ZenoPivot, or other media forms or
media channels, related or connected thereto as may be available
(collectively, the “Zeno Media Service”). The following privacy policy (“Privacy
Policy”) is designed to inform you, as a user of the Zeno Media Service, about
the types of information that Company may gather or collect from you in
connection with your access to the Zeno Media Service. It also is intended to
explain the conditions under which Company uses and discloses
that information, and your rights in relation to that information. Changes to
this Privacy Policy are discussed at the end of this document. Each time you
access the Zeno Media Service, however, the current version of this Privacy
Policy will apply.
Accordingly, each time you access the Zeno Media Service you should check
the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the beginning of this
document) and review any changes since the last time you accessed the
Zeno Media Service.

The Zeno Media Service is hosted in the United States of America (“United
States” or “U.S.”) and is subject to U.S. state and federal law. If you are
accessing the Zeno Media Service from other jurisdictions, please be advised
that you are transferring your personal information to us in the United
States, and by accessing the Zeno Media Service, you consent to that
transfer and use of your personal information in accordance with this
Privacy Policy. You also agree to abide by the applicable laws of applicable
states and U.S. federal law concerning your access to the Zeno Media
Service and your agreements with us. Any persons accessing the Zeno
Media Service from any jurisdiction with laws or regulations governing
personal data collection, use and disclosure different from those of the
jurisdictions mentioned above may only use the Zeno Media Service in a
manner lawful in their jurisdiction. If your access to the Zeno Media Service
would be unlawful in your jurisdiction, please do not access the Zeno Media
Service.
BY ACCESSING THE Zeno Media SERVICE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE
PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
CHILDREN
The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) protects the online
privacy of children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect or
maintain personal information from anyone under the age of 13, unless or
except as permitted by law. Any person who provides personal information
through the Zeno Media Service represents to us that he or she is 13 years of
age or older. If we learn that personal information has been collected from a
listener under 13 years of age through the Zeno Media Service, then we will
take the appropriate steps to cause this information to be deleted. If you are
the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a user of
the Zeno Media Service or has otherwise transferred personal information
to us through the Zeno Media Service, please contact Company using
our contact information below to have that child’s personal information
deleted.

Zeno Media SERVICES GENERALLY
The Zeno Media Service is an interactive service that allows users to access
radio stations around the world through a wide variety of means such as
telephones, browsers, website widgets, players, apps, and mobile devices.
We collect and store both Non-Personally-Identifying Information and
Personally Identifying Information (both defined below) about users and
their habits, activities and preferences when listening to radio programming
offered through the Zeno Media Service. Such information is collected,
retained and used as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
MICROPHONE ACCESS
Users have the opportunity to speak directly with radio broadcasters
through the Zeno Media Service and such broadcasters may initiate such
contact. Such communication may be conducted via traditional telephone
communication, but may also be conducted via a mobile device or browser,
website widget, or player. In order to conduct such communications (other
than via traditional telephone communication), a user must enable the
microphone on the applicable device. ACCORDINGLY, BY ENABLING THE
MICROPHONE ON YOUR DEVICE, YOU ARE INDICATING THAT A
BROADCASTER, OR OTHER RADIO STATION PERSONNEL,
ARE PERMITTED TO CONTACT YOU DIRECTLY USING YOUR MICROPHONE
VIA THE MEANS MADE AVAILABLE THROUGH THE Zeno Media SERVICE.
We cannot control who hears your conversation once you are on the air and
cannot control the broadcasters from re-broadcasting such conversations.
GATHERING, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF NON-PERSONALLY-
IDENTIFYING INFORMATION
Users of the Service Generally “Non-Personally-Identifying Information” is
information that, without the aid of additional information, cannot be
directly associated with a specific person. “Personally-Identifying
Information,” by contrast, is information such as a name, email address or
telephone number that, without more, can be directly associated with a
specific person. Company gathers from users of the Zeno Media Service

Non-Personally-Identifying Information of the sort that devices, depending
on their settings, may make available. That information includes, for users
accessing the Zeno Media Service over the Internet, a user’s Internet
Protocol (IP) address, operating system and browser type, and the locations
of the web pages the user views right before arriving at, while navigating
and immediately after leaving the Zeno Media Service. If you use a mobile
device to access the Zeno Media Service or download any of our
applications, we may collect device information (such as your mobile device
ID, model and manufacturer), operating system and version information,
and IP address. Company collects and analyzes Non-Personally-Identifying
Information gathered from users of the Zeno Media Service to help
Company better understand how the Zeno Media Service is being used, how
to promote the Zeno Media Service, and for the delivery of targeted
advertising. By identifying patterns and trends in usage,including radio
station listening habits and patterns, Company is able to better design the
Zeno Media Service to improve users’ experiences, both in terms of content,
advertising and ease of use. From time to time, Company may also
release the Non-Personally-Identifying Information gathered from the Zeno
Media Service users in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on
trends in the usage of the Zeno Media Service.
Web Cookies
A “Web Cookie” is a string of information which assigns you a unique
identification that a website stores on your computer or device, and that the
user’s browser provides each time the user logs on to or submits a query to
the Zeno Media Service. We use cookies on the Zeno Media Service to keep
track of services you have used and activities you have performed, radio
stations you have listened to and listening and call-in habits, to record, if
applicable, registration information regarding your login name and
password, to record your use preferences, if applicable, to keep you logged
into the Zeno Media Service, if applicable, and to facilitate
purchase procedures, if applicable. Company also uses Web Cookies to track
the pages that users visit and activities performed during each Zeno Media

Service session, both to help Company improve users’ experiences and to
help Company understand how the Zeno Media Service is being used. As
with other Non-Personally-Identifying
Information gathered from users of the Zeno Media Service, Company
analyzes and discloses in aggregated form information gathered using Web
Cookies, so as to help Company, its partners and others better understand
how the Zeno Media Service is being used. USERS WHO DO NOT WISH TO
HAVE WEB COOKIES PLACED ON THEIR COMPUTERS OR DEVICES
SHOULD SET THEIR BROWSERS TO REFUSE WEB COOKIES BEFORE
ACCESSING THE Zeno Media SERVICE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT
CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE Zeno Media SERVICE MAY NOT FUNCTION
PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF WEB COOKIES. USERS WHO
REFUSE WEB COOKIES ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY
RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.
Flash Cookies
“Flash Cookies” are a form of persistent cookies technically called “Local
Shared Objects” (LSOs). Flash Cookies set an LSO to track your use of the
Zeno Media Service. This tracking and storage can occur even after you have
deleted your Web Cookies or opted-out of network advertising. This tracking
sets two cookies on your computer – a standard cookie and a Flash Cookie.
Flash Cookies can be considered to be equivalent to “normal” Web Cookies,
except for a few minor differences. With Flash Cookies your data is stored in
multiple places and it is restored once you delete it. Normal Web Cookies
can be managed via the preferences dialog of most web browsers, but no
similar utility for managing Flash Cookies is included in most web browsers. It
is possible for Flash Cookies to remain on your computer indefinitely because
an expiration date cannot be set for them. As with normal Web Cookies,
a website that placed the Flash Cookie can only access data that it
captured; it is not allowed to read Flash Cookies created by other websites.
Web Beacons
A “Web Beacon” is an object that is embedded in a web page that is usually

invisible to the user and allows website operators to check whether a user
has viewed a particular web page or an email. Company may use Web
Beacons on the Zeno Media Service and in emails to count users who have
visited particular pages, viewed emails, and to deliver co-branded services.
Web Beacons are not used to access users’ Personally-Identifying
Information; they are a technique Company may use to compile aggregated
statistics about the Zeno Media Service usage. Web Beacons collect only a
limited set of information including a Web Cookie number, time and date of a
page or email view, and a description of the page or email on which the Web
Beacon resides. You may not decline Web Beacons, however, they can
be rendered ineffective by declining all Web Cookies or modifying your
browser setting to notify you each time a Web Cookie is tendered and permit
you to accept or decline Web Cookies on an individual basis.
Telephone Access
When you access the Zeno Media Service via a telephone we obtain your
telephone number (unless the caller ID is blocked), keep track of services you
have used and activities you have performed, radio stations you have
listened to and your listening and call-in habits.
Advertising
We or broadcasters may either directly or through third-party companies
serve ads to you when you access the Zeno Media Service. Advertisers may
use information about your visits to and use of the Zeno Media Service
(including, without limitation, stations accessed, listening habits, and location
of accessing telephone number) that are contained in Web Cookies, Flash
Cookies or that we gather when you access the Zeno Media Service via a
telephone (wireless or wired device) or other application or access method in
order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of
interest to you. We also allow advertisers to choose the characteristics
of listeners who will be presented with their advertisements and we may use
any of the non-personally identifiable attributes we have collected to select
the appropriate audience for those advertisements. Advertisements may be

served via SMS/text messages, voice messages, email, push messaging or
other means from Zeno Media or affiliated third parties. If you are accessing
the Zeno Media Service via the Internet, then using a tool created by the
Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third party ad
servers’ and networks’ Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like
more information about this practice and to know your choices about not
having this information used by these companies, please follow the following
link: http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. Please contact
us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising
companies we are currently using to serve ads.
Analytics
One of the third party services that we use to track activity related to our
service, e.g., by placing cookies, is Google Analytics. We may use third-party
vendors, including Google, who use first-party cookies (such as the Google
Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie)
together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past activity on
our websites and applications, including Google Analytics for Display
Advertising. If you do not want any information to be collected and used by
Google Analytics, you can install an opt-out in your web browser (https://
tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) and/or opt out from Google Analytics
for Display Advertising or the Google Display Network. You can do so by
using Google’s Ads Settings (www.google.com/settings/ads). Aggregated
and Non-Personally-Identifying Information We may share aggregated and
Non-Personally Identifying Information we collect under any of the above
circumstances. We may also share it with third parties and our affiliate
companies to develop and deliver targeted advertising on the Zeno
Media Service and on websites of third parties. We may combine Non-
Personally Identifying Information we collect with additional Non-Personally
Identifying Information collected from other sources. We also may share
aggregated information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers
and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For
example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to the Zeno

Media Service and the most popular features or services accessed. This
information does not contain any Personally-Identifying Information and
may be used to develop website content and services that we hope you
and other listeners will find of interest and to target content and advertising.
Mobile Device Additional Terms
Geo-Location Information. Unless we have received your prior consent, we
do not access or track any specific location-based information from your
mobile device at any time while downloading or using our mobile
applications or the Zeno Media Services. However, based upon your IP
address, the telephone number that you use to access the Zeno Media
Service, Wi Fi network data or cell tower triangulation, we may record
general non-specific locations. However, we may also automatically collect
anonymous information about you when you have geographical location
tools on your Internet-enabled device which have not been disabled. We
may also collect anonymous information about you whenever you
deliberately interact with one of our ads containing a quick response code or
follow instructions to send a text, or visit a URL. If you have geo-location
tools on your Internet-enabled device which you have not disabled, we
automatically receive information on your device’s location and may use it to
comply with our contractual arrangements which restrict our sending certain
programming channels outside of defined areas, such as when you want to
listen to the Zeno Media service while in another country.
Push Notifications. We may send you push notifications if you choose
to receive them for other service-related matters. If you wish to opt-out
from receiving these types of communications you may request to have
them stopped at any time via preferences on your mobile device. Mobile
Analytics. We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand
the functionality of our mobile software on your mobile device. This software
may record information such as how often you use the application, the
events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance
data, and where the application was downloaded from.

COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY-
IDENTIFYING INFORMATION
Information Collection
As defined above, Personally-Identifying Information is information that can
be directly associated with a specific person. Company may collect
Personally Identifying Information from and about the Zeno Media Service
users. Much of the Personally-Identifying Information collected by Company
about users is information provided by users themselves when (1) registering
for the Zeno Media Service, (2)dialing in to the Zeno Media Service, (3)
logging in with social network credentials, (4) participating in polls, contests,
surveys or other features of the Zeno Media Service, or responding to offers
or advertisements on the Zeno Media Service, (5) communicating with us, or
(6) signing up to receive newsletters or other communications. That
Personally Identifying Information may include each user’s name, address,
email address, and telephone number. We also may request information
about your interests and activities, your gender, age, date of birth, language
preference, hometown and other demographic information, and
other relevant information as determined by Company from time to time.
Additionally, when you access the Zeno Media Service from a telephone or
mobile device we may also obtain your telephone number which may also be
used for tracking your use of the Zeno Media Service. Users of the Zeno
Media Service are under no obligation to provide Company with Personally-
Identifying Information of any kind, though some information, like a
telephone number, may be provided automatically when using the Zeno
Media Service. We may also use reverse look up functionality in order to
obtain the name of a person associated with a particular phone number. We
store Personally-Identifying Information and linked Non-Personally-
Identifiable Information that we gather about you through the Zeno Media
Service, through social media, through linked social media applications, or
that you give to us voluntarily in any other way, and we may use it in
accordance with this Privacy Policy.

BY REGISTERING WITH OR USING THE ZENO MEDIA SERVICE, YOU
CONSENT TO THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONALLY
IDENTIFYING INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS “COLLECTION, USE
AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION”
SECTION.
Online Postings
We may provide areas or features on or via the Zeno Media Service where
you can post reviews, provide audio or other content during interactive
sessions, and other information relating to your activities on or via the Zeno
Media Service. Such postings are governed by our Terms of Use. In addition,
such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed
on the subject of your posting. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose
personal information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will
be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example,
if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages. We
cannot control who reads your posting or what other users may do with the
information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise
discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. USERS
ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY LOSS OF PRIVACY OR OTHER
HARM RESULTING FROM THEIR VOLUNTARY DISCLOSURE OF
PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION.
Company Communications
We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you
notifications regarding new services or products offered by Company that
we think you may find valuable. If we have obtained proper authorization, we
may also contact you via email, telephone, text or push notification. We may
also send you service-related announcements from time to time through the
general operation of the Service. Generally, you may opt out of receiving
such communications, though we reserve the right to email you notices
about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

Social Media
We may provide you the option to connect your account, if applicable, on
the Zeno Media Service to your account on some social networking sites
(such as via Facebook Connect) for the purpose of logging in, uploading
information or enabling certain features on the Zeno Media Service. When
logging in using your social network credentials, such as your Facebook
account, we may collect the Personally Identifying Information you have
made publicly available in Facebook, such as your name, profile picture,
cover photo, username, gender, friends network, age range, locale, friend
list, and any other information you have made public. We may also obtain
other non-public information from the social network website with
your permission. Once connected, others may also be able to see
information about your social network, such as the size of your network and
your friends, including common friends. By connecting your account on the
Zeno Media Service to your account on
any social networking site, you hereby consent to the continuous release
of information about you to us. We will not send any of your account
information to the connected social networking site without first disclosing
that to you. Each social network may further allow you to set privacy controls
around your information on their system, and our collection of information
will always follow such controls and permissions. This feature is subject to
continuous change and improvement by us and each social networking site
involved, and therefore the available features and shared information are
subject to change without notice to you.
Company Disclosures
Company will disclose Personally-Identifying Information under the
following circumstances: Broadcasters/Advertisers. Through your access to
the Zeno Media Service, we collect a variety of information regarding how
you use the Zeno Media Service, and this information can be linked to
Personally-Identifiable Information we have obtained about you. We may
disclose this information to broadcasters of radio stations that you access
via the Zeno Media Service as well as to our advertisers. Broadcasters may

use the information we disclose about you only for their internal purposes,
such as improving programming, identifying you if you call in to a radio show,
contacting you as a listener of their programming, in order to deliver
advertising, and for related purposes. Marketing Communications. Unless
users opt-out from receiving Company marketing materials, Company may
email, SMS/text, deliver recorded messages and otherwise communicate
with users, or contact users via other means (all in compliance with
applicable law), about products and services that Company believes may be
of interest to them and Company also will provide users’ email information
(and other contact information) to third parties, so that those third parties
may directly contact users about additional products and services. If a user
wishes to opt-out of receiving marketing materials from Company, user may
do so by following the unsubscribe link in email communications, by going to
your account settings (if applicable) or contacting us using the contact
information below. Similarly, to cease having your email or other contact
information provided to third parties, you may do so by going to your
account settings (if applicable) or contacting us using the contact
information below. Even after opting-out, a user may continue to receive
marketing emails or other communications from third parties to
whom Company already has provided the user’s email or other contact
information. Users will be responsible for directly contacting such third
parties to request cessation of further marketing communications.
Disclosure to Trusted Third Parties at Your Request. When using the Zeno
Media Service, we may provide you with advertisements,
promotions, sweepstakes and offers from Company or third party providers.
If you choose to accept any such offers, or agree to listen to or view
additional information concerning the advertisement or promotion, or to be
contacted by Company or a third-party, you may either (depending on the
situation) be transferred to and directly provide your information in
connection with the advertisement or promotion to such third party provider,
or we will provide your information to the third party provider. Your
information will not be transferred until you actually agree to listen to or

view additional information, or agree to be contacted, or accept the offer, as
the case may be. You may opt-out of such activities at any time up until this
point. Please refer to the third party provider’s own privacy policy if you have
any questions regarding how your information is used by such providers.
Please be aware that these offers may be presented while using the Zeno
Media Service on your telephone (wired or wireless device), via a website or
browser, website widget, player, application, or otherwise. We do this to
provide a seamless experience. Although these offers may have the look and
feel of the Zeno Media Services, you will be submitting your information
directly to the third-party advertiser. You agree that we will not be
responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result
of any such dealings, including the sharing of the information you supply to
us with third party providers described here, or as the result of the presence
of such providers on a Company website. By Law or to Protect Rights. When
we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate,
prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or
other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our
Company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law
or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce our Terms of Use or other
agreements or policies, in response to a subpoena or similar investigative
demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement
or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to
defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases,
we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
Affiliates. We may share some or all of your personal information with
our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this
Privacy Policy. Affiliates would include a parent company or any subsidiaries,
joint venture partners, or other companies that we control or that is
under common control with us. Such intercompany transfers may be to and
from the United States and any other country in which we or our agents
maintain facilities for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy, as well as
for storage, processing or other business use as permitted under this

Privacy Policy. By accessing or using the Zeno Media Service you consent to
the /transfer of your personal information among these entities, including
those located outside of your country of residence.
Third Party Service Providers. We may share your Personally-
Identifying Information, which may include your name and contact
information with our authorized service providers that perform certain
services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling orders, providing
customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales
analysis, supporting our website functionality, supporting or maintaining our
service platform or technologies, and supporting contests, sweepstakes,
surveys and other features offered through the Zeno Media Service. We may
also share your name, contact information and credit card information with
our authorized service providers who process credit card payments. These
service providers may have access to personal information needed to
perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such
information for any other purpose. Business Transfers; Bankruptcy. Company
reserves the right to transfer all Personally-Identifying Information in its
possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition,
or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Company’s assets. Other
than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and
disclosure of all transferred Personally-Identifying Information will be
subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice
of that new privacy policy and are given an opportunity to affirmatively opt-
out of it. Personally-Identifying Information submitted or collected after a
transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by the
successor organization.
General Use
We use the Personally-Identifying Information in the data we maintain
about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past
activities in connection with the Zeno Media Service to: deliver the products
and services that you have requested, manage your account, if applicable,

and provide you with customer support, communicate with you by email,
postal mail, telephone and/or mobile devices about products or services
that may be of interest to you either from us, our affiliate companies or other
third parties, develop and display content and advertising tailored to your
interests on the Zeno Media Service and other sites, resolve disputes,
troubleshoot problems, measure consumer interest in our services, inform
you of updates, customize your experience, detect and protect us
against error, fraud and other criminal activity, enforce our Terms of Use,
and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. At times, we may
look across multiple
users to identify problems. In particular, we may examine your Personally
Identifying Information to identify users using multiple listener IDs or aliases.
We may compare and review your Personally-Identifying Information for
accuracy and to detect errors and omissions. We may use financial
information or payment method to process payment for any purchases
made through the Zeno Media Service, enroll you in the discount, rebate,
and other programs in which you elect to participate, to protect against or
identify possible fraudulent transactions, and otherwise as needed to
manage our business.
CONTESTS, GIVEAWAYS AND SURVEYS
From time to time, Company may offer users the opportunity to participate
in contests, giveaways and other promotions. Any information submitted in
connection with such activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy
Policy. From time to time, Company may also ask users to participate in
surveys designed to help Company improve the Zeno Media Service. Any
Personally-Identifying Information provided to Company in connection with
any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to
third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in non-personally-
identifying, aggregated form.
COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION BY THIRD PARTIES GENERALLY
Third parties are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy, with

respect to Personally-Identifying Information that users provide directly to
those third parties or that those third parties collect for themselves. These
third parties include advertisers, providers of games, utilities, widgets and a
variety of other third party applications accessible through the Zeno Media
Service. Company neither owns nor controls the third-parties and
applications accessible through the Zeno Media Service. Thus, this Privacy
Policy does not apply to information provided to or gathered by the third
parties. Before visiting a third-party, or using a third party application,
whether by means of a link on the Zeno Media Service, directly through the
Zeno Media Service, or otherwise, and before providing any Personally-
Identifying Information to any such third party, users should inform
themselves of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third parties,
and should take those steps necessary to, in those users’ discretion, protect
their privacy.
SECURITY
We take security of your Personally-Identifying Information seriously and
use reasonable electronic, personnel, and physical measures to protect it
from loss, theft, alteration, or misuse. However, please be advised that even
the best security measures cannot fully eliminate all risks. We cannot
guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We are
not responsible for third party circumvention of any privacy settings or
security measures.
Wireless Consent Policy
You authorize your wireless operator (AT&T, Sprint, T-Mobile, US Cellular,
Verizon, or any other branded wireless operator) to use your mobile number,
name, address, email, network status, customer type, customer role, billing
type, mobile device identifiers (IMSI and IMEI) and other subscriber status
details, if available, solely to allow verification of your identity and to
compare information you have provided to Zeno Media with your wireless
operator account profile information for the duration of the business
relationship. See our Privacy Policy for how we treat your data.

Social Media
By using this service you authorize your wireless operator (AT&T, Sprint, T-
Mobile, US Cellular, Verizon, or any other branded wireless operator) to use
your mobile number, name, address, email, network status, customer type,
customer role, billing type, mobile device identifiers (IMSI and IMEI) and
other subscriber status details, if available, solely to allow verification of your
identity and to compare information you have provided to Zeno Media with
your wireless operator account profile information for the duration of the
business relationship. See our Privacy Policy for how we treat your data.
PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES
Company may, in its sole discretion, change this Privacy Policy from time to
time. Any and all changes to Company’s Privacy Policy will be reflected on
this page and the date new versions are posted will be stated at the top of
this Privacy Policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy
applies to all information that we have about you and your account, if
applicable. Users should regularly check this page for any changes to its
Privacy Policy. Company will always post new versions of the Privacy Policy
on the Zeno Media website.
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light”
law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain
from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal
information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing
purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information
would include a list of the categories of personal information that was
shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we
shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a
California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit
your request in writing to our privacy officer as listed below.

DO NOT TRACK POLICY
The Zeno Media Service does not respond to “Do Not Track” signals or
mechanisms.
CONTACT
If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact our
privacy officer at:
Privacy Officer
Zeno Media LLC
Email: support@zenomedia.io
Phone: (212) 822-3460
